[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 8, "question": "He sent me two letters saying by the way, can you send me some stimulus money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "Mr. Vice President, I know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "How plausible is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, you know, the buck has to stop somewhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "That part is hard to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "So, my immediate question to you is, does your dad do that scary laugh to his own kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Look, my dad's a wonderful, wonderful father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Did you feel in the moment that your dad had won quite easily?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "EAU BIDEN: Well, look, you know, I thought he did what we set out to do and that's communicate directly to the American people what he and the president want to continue doing for the middle class.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Does he feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "If the Republicans were to win and actually put more troops in Afghanistan, what would that do, do you think, to the morale of the military?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "IN", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Look, the military does what it's asked to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "You know what the unemployment rate in Scranton is today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I sure do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Scranton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "If you're the guy who's being Paul Ryan for days on end, how do you feel watching the real thing happening without you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Oh, that's a very good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Why did not more people think that your man won?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, it's hard to know how to read these polls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "When you were being Paul Ryan, were you nervously gulping water every three minutes in the prep?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, I didn't do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Do you actually put on a Paul Ryan voice when you're pretending to be him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, look, I'm not trying to go for any Academy Awards on the acting side.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Biden"]}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "But what -- who do you think won last night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I think Joe Biden won the debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "IN", "NNPS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Kristen, do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "No, I don't agree with that, but I think it is possible for Republicans to really think their guy won and for Democrats to really think their guy won.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Kristen Soltis, what did you make of his extraordinary water intake because Joe Biden didn't drink at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I think staying hydrated is really important.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kristen Soltis", "Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Biden", "Paul Ryan"]}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Carol Roth, would you rather have a presidential, vice presidential candidate who drinks a lot of water in a nervous way or one like Joe Biden who toughs it out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Well, I think Joe Biden clearly had a lot of Mountain Dew before he went on the debate, where Paul Ryan favored the water.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol Roth", "Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Biden", "Paul Ryan"]}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "WRB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "As it went on, I found it increasingly infectious and began laughing with him, which can't help Ryan, can it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Look, I don't think how much Joe Biden smiled or how hydrated Paul Ryan is, is going to decide the election, but I agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "You did ask for stimulus money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Sure he did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "So he should be grateful, really, to the government for providing it, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "No, he shouldn't be grateful about the stimulus.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "It's very, very important that Barack Obama comes back with a win, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Well, it depends on who you're voting for.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "No, no, I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "If he lost by the same degree that he lost the other night, wouldn't that really be the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Look what's happened since.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Governor Romney"]}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Kristen, last word to you, how do you think it will go on Tuesday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "I think you are going to see another really great performance from Governor Romney.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"], "PERSON": ["Kristen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Yes, and I had to go feel really uncomfortable until I had a good night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Can you be as good sober?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "I think I'm there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago", "Eagles"]}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "I could give you five hours to relive the party, what would you go for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "We played in Chicago back then, the Eagles did, and we had a -- we were on top of the world and we had a great show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Belushi was the top dog, wasn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Belushi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How are you seeing it this time around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I'm historically a Democrat, but I don't agree with either of them 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "121012pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Who will it be or haven't you decided yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Congress is the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]